{
    "id": "226e05e533a04185a1ff6a840cbd8c53",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You must abide …………………. the terms of this agreement.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "by",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3e4b87148632466f999dcb52bbe7a0df"
        },
        {
            "question": "This part of the country abounds ....................... rare metals.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d3c7ecf50e04471ea76595d349247e0c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has been absent .....................… the class for two weeks now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "to",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "11645192df5f4e79956d13940ebddcf8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was absorbed ....................... his work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6426d1cd0d814795bda7f978a5471b57"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must abstain ...................... smoking and drinking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "from",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "eb18521e284347babc4edc8e0528b5a8"
        },
        {
            "question": "We cannot accede .....................… this request.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0736e19fbf8846cda1fb9d178f35414f"
        },
        {
            "question": "This suggestion is not acceptable ………………….. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9d3888679c3a4a25978077258086e786"
        },
        {
            "question": "Millions of people still do not have access ..................... . the internet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d6e0a7e55f92444eb0d823bb4ed30133"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was accused ………………….. theft.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "against"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "93807eaa672b41dabe68a3bf69a691a8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not acquainted ...................... him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fe13b0f98f104b0d982b436851ba93db"
        }
    ]
}